seoulradar.com 2014-06-28

# Privacy Policy | Trip to KoreaㅣSeoulRadar

**Privacy Policy  
**  
(1) In order to improve the Company’s services and system 

Seoul Radar Inc., Ltd (hereafter, “Company”) will strive to protect the personal information obtained from customers (hereafter “User”) on the basis of the following policies.   If you provide us with personal information on our Site, please do so after carefully reading and understanding this Privacy Policy (hereafter “Policy”). 

1.  Personal information

In this Policy, personal information refers to the following items that can be used to identify the User:  name, age, gender, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number, etc. 

2\. Personal information purpose of use

The customer’s personal information is collected and use for the following purposes.   

(2) When the User uses services as a member of the Company’s Site 

(3) To provide products and services when the User uses or purchases the Company’s products and services. 

(4) To respond to customer requests and inquiries. 

(5) Marketing activities for the products and services of the Company and our partners 

(6) When contacting hotels and beauty salons regarding the usage and purchase information of Users.

(7) When related to other activities in the normal course of business. 

3.       Management of Personal information

We manage your personal information using the framework described below.

(1) The Company requires its employees to strictly observe the Privacy Policy and Guideline when putting into place the necessary internal systems and handling personal information.  

(2) Personal information will only be used by the Company’s employees that need it to provide services to the User.  The Company will take precautionary measures to protect personal information and with regards to the storage and management of mediums that contain personal information. 

(3)Access rights management policies will be enforced with regards to personal information stored in the system allowing access and use only to employees who need the information to perform their duties. 

(4) For the security of personal information data transmission over the Internet,  SSL encryption, that is the industry standard, is used on web pages that require it.

4.  Personal information given to Third Parties

The  Company may outsource all or some of the actual work that requires access to personal information.  The Company appropriately manages the handling oe personal information with regards to disclosing it to Third Parties.  The Company will not disclose nor provide Users’ personal information to Third Parties without prior approval of Users with the exception of the above.  When Users’ personal information is disclosed or provided to outsourcing firms that the Company uses or between Third Parties, the Company will separately investigate the parties receiving the personal information, sign a non-disclosure agreement with them and appropriately treat and manage the personal information. 

5\. Disclosure of Personal information

• The Company will not disclose User’s personal information to Third Party without consent.  However, in the following cases, exceptions may be made. 

(1) If there is a request, based on the law, from public institutions such as the police and courts.

(2) If there is a special provision in laws and regulations that requires disclosure.

(3) When it is not possible to obtain the consent of the User because there is a possibility that the Users’ or Third Parties’ life, physical body or property may be impaired. 

(4) When it is necessary to defend or protect the Company’s property or services, due to an infringement of the law or of any of the User Agreements, and it is impossible to obtain consent from the User. 

• If there is a request for disclosure of personal information from our customers, disclosure will only be made if the identification of the requesting party can be confirmed to be of the User whose information is requested.   

6.  User management strategies for Safety Purposes

Users’ personal information is protected thoroughly with the use of a password. Confirmation of and changes in personal information is only possible by the Users themselves who know the password, hence Users must not tell their passwords to anyone else. The Company encourages Users to pay particular attention when using the Site on shared computers in public places (company or school, library, Internet cafe, etc), and to log out and close the web browser after using the Sites.

7.  Complaints and Inquiries regarding the handling of Personal information

For inquiries and complaints about the handling of personal information, please contact the personal information inquiries desk below.
